WITCHES ARE REAL!
Roald Dahl's The Witches is a comedy, fantasy,
family film directed by Robert Zemeckis.
In late 1967, a young orphaned boy goes to live with his loving
grandma in the rural Alabama town of Demopolis.
As the boy and his grandmother encounter some deceptively glamorous but thoroughly
diabolical witches, she wisely whisks him away to a seaside resort.
Regrettably, they arrive at precisely the same time that
the world's Grand High Witch has gathered.
Grand High Witch, played by Anne Hathaway.
Grandma, played by Octavia Spencer.
Mr Stringer, played by Stanley Tucci.
Hero Boy, played by Jahzir Bruno.
Older Hero (voice), played by Chris Rock.
Bruno Jenkins, played by Codie-Lei Eastick.
The Witches (also known as Roald Dahl's The Witches), is a 2020 dark fantasy comedy horror film co-produced and directed by Robert
Zemeckis, who co-wrote the screenplay with Kenya Barris and Guillermo del Toro, based on the 1983 novel The Witches by Roald Dahl.
It is the second film adaptation of the novel, following The Witches (1990).
The film stars Anne Hathaway, Octavia Spencer, Stanley Tucci, Kristin
Chenoweth, and Jahzir Bruno, with narration by Chris Rock.
The Witches was released on the streaming service HBO Max in the United States on October 22, 2020,
and had a theatrical release in some markets beginning on October 28, by Warner Bros.
The film explores themes of hotel, witch, based on
novel or book, mouse, transformation.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.